superbiiz.com 2019-04-21

# Computer Parts, CPUs, Memory, Servers and more! - SuperBiiz.com

**Privacy Statement**

We base our business on the trust you place in us. Our privacy statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. We have created this statement to protect your privacy.

 **Cookies**  
Our site uses cookies to provide our customers with a better shopping experience. Information stored in our cookies is encrypted and include only customer log-in data. The cookies help to identify you during your visit, allowing us to personalize your shopping experience (like storing items in your shopping cart in between visits). You will need to set your browser to accept cookies to allow this feature as part of your shopping experience.

If you arrive to our site from a link on another website, we may be tracking that click information in order to understand where our visitors come from. We also track your activity on our website to learn how our visitors interact with the pages of our website and to improve the content and experience in the future.

Third party partners, including Google, use cookies or similar technologies to analyze user behavior on our site, serve the badge on our website, and display relevant advertising content based on a user's prior visits to our website. We also use DoubleClick remarketing code to log when users view specific pages. This allows us to provide targeted advertising in the future. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.

 **IP Address**  
Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information such as regional location. We may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. **Security**  
This Website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. Our secure server uses advanced encryption and firewall technology to keep your personal information private. Our secure server layer (SSL) software completely encrypts the information you submit through our secure Order Form so that it cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system. **Electronic Forms**  
Please help us to ensure your privacy by not sharing your account name and password with anyone.

Our site provides online Account Forms for customers to make purchases, facilitate a return, and to request information from Superbiiz.com. In order to process an order, we collect personal information including name, phone number, shipping and billing addresses, email address, and credit card payment information. This personal information collected will be used to contact customers regarding their order (order confirmation, stock updates, shipment notification, etc.), to prevent and detect fraud, to update our records about your account, to verify your identity, and prevent money laundering. Name and shipping addresses will be used to send orders. Credit card information collected is only used to bill the customer for products and services ordered by the customer. In order to facilitate a return, we provide a form to submit to our RMA department. The information we request on this form (Name, Address, Email, Invoice#, and reason for return) is only used to verify the order, verify the account, and to provide more details on your request for return and to communicate with you after submitting the request. 

The information we hold about you is confidential. We will only disclose it outside of our company when you give us consent, it is needed by reputable third-party partners involved in products and services we may offer you, it is needed by us or others to investigate, report or prevent crime, if the law permits or requires it, or if any regulatory or governmental body requests or requires it, even without your consent. We may also use your information for research or statistical analysis to improve our services.

 **Lawful Use**  
You must not use any computer equipment, computers, network resources, goods sold, or services provided by us for an illegal purpose, including but not limited to, violation of export control laws or moneylaundering, or for accessing, receiving or transmitting any material deemed illegal, indecent, offensive or otherwise unacceptable under US law. **Children**  
Our sites are general audience sites intended for purchasers with valid payment types and we do not sell products for purchase by children. We do not intentionally or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you believe we may have collected personal information from a child, please email [support@superbiiz.com](mailto:support@superbiiz.com) so we can take immediate action. **Corrections/Updates**  
You may access or correct some personal and account information maintained in your account through our website by logging into My Account and clicking on "Edit My Account" button. Information regarding your current account will be displayed. Make the necessary changes and click on the "Update Account" button. Your account will be updated. To correct or delete any other information about you or content you post on our sites, or to exercise any right to restrict or object to processing or data portability, please contact your account manager. If you do not know your account manager, simply contact us at [support@superbiiz.com](mailto:support@superbiiz.com) from the email address tied to your account. We may request additional information to confirm your identity with the request and reserve the right to decline requests unless required by applicable law. **Special Contests or Promotions**  
Occasionally, we will run special contests or other promotions on our site that will request for contact information or other demographic data. If you are selected as a winner, we will send your prize to the address you entered into our system, and notify you by email. We may also use your contact information to notify you about future promotions, specials, or new additions to our site. **Opt-out/Unsubscribe**  
When creating a new account, users have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. Simply uncheck the box next to "I would like to receive newsletters ...". You can also change this at anytime by logging into "My Account" and pressing the "Edit my Account". Uncheck the box next to "I would like to receive newsletters ...". Finally, depress the "Update Account" button. We will immediately stop sending email on our offers and other special promotions. **Information Sharing**  

  * Affiliated Institutions - SuperBiiz may share your information with our affiliates for business, operational, promotional and marketing purposes.
  * Service Providers - SuperBiiz may share your information with our service providers for business purposes, such as advertising, technical supporting, conducting surveys and fulfilling orders.
  * Reviews about Services - By submitting reviews about SuperBiiz on the site, you give us the permission to reprint and use in connection with our business. Please note that any information you include in a review may be read, collected or used by anyone.
  * Reviews about Products - By submitting reviews about products on the site, you give us the permission to reprint and use in connection with our business. Please note that any information you include in a review may be read, collected or used by anyone.
  * Links to External Websites - This site contains links to other Websites to enhance your online shopping experience, including social media sharing features and manufacturer microsites. Links to third party websites are provided solely for your convenience and any submission of data to such websites shall be at your sole risk. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. We recommend that you review the privacy notice of each website you visit.

**Feedback**  
Our site also provides the opportunity for customers to share information about their shopping experience or to review a product they purchased. By posting a testimonial or a review about a product on our website, you give us permission to reprint or use the testimonial or review in connection with our business with or without name credit and without compensation. This feedback content given in this manner becomes property of Superbiiz.com. Your personal contact information will not be disclosed if we use your testimonial or review. Please make sure you do not share any other personally identifiable information in these input boxes as this information is posted on our website for the general public. Should you decide you no longer wish to have your testimonial or product review content visible on our site, please contact [support@superbiiz.com](mailto:support@superbiiz.com). from your account email and we will assist.
